https://skyshots.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
SkyShots Photography recognizes that respecting user privacy over the Internet is of utmost importance. This privacy statement is designed to provide information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site: www.skyshots.com. The Site is operated by SkyShots Photography of Mechanicsville, Virginia. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our site coordinator at
tomstiles@skyshots.com or by postal mail to: SkyShots Photography, 9567 Winnepeg Court, Virginia 23116.
Identifying Information: In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to process an order, offer services that require registration, assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you. Generally, SkyShots Photography requests identifying information when you submit a request for information via our web form.
In these instances, SkyShots Photography will ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number and other appropriate information needed to provide you with the information you request. In all instances, if you receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to “unsubscribe” to these mailings at any time.
What SkyShots Photography Will Do With Your Information: If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by SkyShots Photography and will only be used by SkyShots Photography to support your customer relationship with us. We will not add you to a mailing list, or newsletter without your registration for this service. We will only contact you if further information is required from you to complete a service.
What Others May Do With Your Information: SkyShots Photography does not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through our Site (such as your name or email address) to any outside organization for use in its marketing or solicitations. From time to time SkyShots Photography may use agents or contractors who will have access to your personal information to perform services for SkyShots Photography (such as database maintenance), however, they are required by us to keep the information confidential and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services for SkyShots Photography. In addition, SkyShots Photography may also share aggregate information about its customers and its web site visitors to advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we might share that our users are x percent PCs users and y percent Macintosh users. None of this information, however, will contain personal, identifying information about our users.
SkyShots Photography may from time to time revise its privacy policy. You should therefore periodically visit this page, so you are aware of any such revisions. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.
E-mail: tomstiles@skyshots.com
